Medical Sales Representative I ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99 Email: info@qwikresume.com Website: www.qwikresume.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/qwikresume Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama.

Objective

An accomplished Medical Sales Representative I with 14 plus years of experience and successfully driving revenue, and net contribution growth. Strong sales experience including training doctors to bill for services, in-service training, Capital Equipment(\$5k to \$20k), B2B, marketing. Call points to doctors, nurses, office managers, and medical assistants. Great communication skills, Acclivus training, training sales team, presentations. Proficient in Spanish.

Skills

Negotiation, Adaptability, Ability Work Under Pressure, Decision Making, Conflict Resolution

Work Experience

Medical Sales Representative I

Global Sleep/emblem Resources - February 2006 - Present

- Assisting the Territory Manager in achieving sales results at or above established quotas for total and individual product segments.
- Additional responsibilities will include managing, directing, and assisting any authorized product distributor.
- Supporting Territory Managers, accounts and patients within the geography.
- Becoming a customer penetration and relationship development specialist to develop innovative design-wins by linking the customer's technical requirements / needs with the Companys vast design and development options coupled with our extensive product line variants.
- Becoming a product technical and application knowledge authority.
- Establishing rapport with our top accounts, ensuring that the product remains the preferred connector supplier and developing a territory plan to guarantee success and growth.
- Professionally built strong, solid and trustworthy relationships with targeted physicians, offices and nurses. Incorporated the " platinum rule" with physicians and tailored product presentations to their specific needs and personalities.

Medical Sales Representative

Global Sleep - February 2004 - 2006

- Utilized the technical sales experience to focus on selling and developing accounts that present the highest ROI for the sales efforts.
- Teamed with all the departments and divisions worldwide to deliver design wins and develop state-of-the-art customer solutions.
- Communicated the vision, concept or technically detailed material without information loss to the customer.
- Complied with all Safety policies and procedures at all times while conducting company business.
- Maximize sales with targets set by the company.
- Effectively managed and prioritized time to complete administrative activities daily.

٠	Understood and utilized the most up-to-date clinical studies to educate the customers and anticipate questions/concerns about the products.
Education	
	Bachelor Of Science in Kinesiology - 1995 to 1997(University Of Texas At Pan American - Edinburg, TX)Associate in Arts - 1995(University Of Texas At Brownsville - Brownsville, TX)